whichwich.com 2013-05-18

# Legal and Privacy | Which Wich® Superior Sandwiches

**Terms of Use**  
Welcome to the Which Wich® Website, 

 (the “Site”). By using this Website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set forth in these terms of use. If you do not agree to the terms of use, please do not use the Site. Which Wich may from time to time modify or revise the terms by updating the site. Please periodically check the terms of use for changes. Your continued use of this site constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the Terms of Use, including any changes we have made.

  **Proprietary Rights and Restrictions**  
This Site and its content, including without limitation all informational text, headers, custom graphics and button icons, photographs, audio, video, messages, files, documents, sound, images, or other materials (collectively referred to as “content”) are the property of Which Wich, Inc. and/or its affiliates or licensors. The Site is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws.

  The Site and its contents are intended solely for personal, noncommercial use by the users our Site. The content on the Site may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, including by e-mail or other electronic means. Any modification of the content, use of the content on any website or networked computer environment, or use of content for any purpose other than personal, noncommercial use is a violation of the copyright, trademark, and other proprietary rights in the content and is strictly prohibited.

  **Links**  
This site may contain links to websites operated by other parties. The linked sites are not under control of Which Wich, and Which Wich is not responsible for the content available on any other websites linked to ours. You acknowledge and agree that your access or use of any linked site is at your own risk.

  **Submissions**  
We appreciate your comments, feedback and remarks. By submitting content to the Site, including remarks, suggestions, ideas, graphics, or other information communicated to us though you, the submission will become our property, including future rights associated with such submissions. You acknowledge that you are responsible for the material you submit, and you, not us, have full responsibility for the message, including reliability, appropriateness, originality, and copyright.

  **Information We Collect**  
You do not have to provide any information to us in order to use our Site. The only information we collect from you is information you choose to submit to us. This includes comments, feedback forms, and requests for information.

  Some areas of the site require registration for use. In those instances, we require that you register information with us. You must complete the registration process by providing us with current, complete, accurate information as prompted by the form(s). You further agree to maintain or promptly update any registration information in order to keep it true, accurate, and correct.

  As a general practice, we do not sell your personally identifiable information to third parties. We may access, use, or disclose your personally identifiable information to operate, maintain, service, or improve our site. Generally, personal information that you provide through our Site is information we may seek to enhance our customers experience in Which Wich restaurants or the Which Wich Site.

  We use third-party suppliers and service providers to facilitate our Site and may take personal information available to them to the extent necessary for site hosting. Whenever we do this, we require that our third-party suppliers and service providers agree to maintain the confidentiality of the personal information we provide to them.

  Which Wich is concerned about the safety and privacy of all its users, particularly children. Which Wich will not knowingly collect information from users under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide us with any personal information.

  **E-mail Submissions**  
E-mail submissions may not be secure over the internet. Please consider this fact before e-mailing any personal or confidential information.

  **Contacting You**  
Occasionally, we may send you e-mail communication to provide information or offers that we think may be of interest to you. You may choose not to receive additional e-mail from us by following the “unsubscribe” procedures in the e-mail you may receive.

  **Employment Opportunities**  
The positions listed on this Site may include opportunities with locations owned and operated by our franchisees, as well as locations owned and operated by Which Wich and its affiliates. The positions and franchise locations may be subject to different terms and conditions including but not limited to benefits, employment policies, etc. We accept no responsibility or liability with respect to the terms and conditions of employment with a franchise restaurant. Any postings on this site do not represent an offer for employment. Any offer must be made by an authorized representative of Which Wich, for company-operated locations, or franchisees, for franchise-operated locations.

  **Franchise Opportunities**  
Some materials on this Site describe Which Wich’s franchise program. They do not constitute an offer or sale of a franchise. Such offering is only commenced by delivering you a prospectus in compliance with applicable law, including, without limitation, the Federal Trade Commission’s guidelines on franchising and various state laws regulating the sale of franchise opportunities.

  **Catering, Retail, and Gift Cards**  
We may use third-party service providers to facilitate the catering, shopping, or gift card ordering services that we make available though the Site. The information you submit while placing a catering, retail shopping, or gift card order, including your name, address, phone number, and credit card information, may be collected by our third-party service provider. Which Wich will not share this information with other third parties. We require that our catering, retail shopping, and gift card service providers maintain your information on a secure server and use industry-standard technology and security procedures for all payment processing. The products and services that we and our service providers offer are entirely voluntary. It is your choice to purchase these products and to participate in our feedback surveys.

  **Our Limitations**  
We respect your privacy. Due to existing legal and technical fluctuations, however, we cannot ensure that your personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties in ways not described in this policy. We may disclose such information to third parties as we believe necessary or appropriate in connection with any merger or consolidation with or sale of our assets. We may also be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about to private entities, law enforcement, or other government officials as we believe necessary or appropriate to address to resolve inquiries or problems.

  **Governing Law, Locations, and Miscellaneous**  
You agree that the terms of use are governed by the laws of the State of Texas (notwithstanding any conflict of law principles). If any provisions of these terms shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from the terms and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. These terms are effective unless and until terminated by Which Wich, Inc. No waiver by either party for any breach or default hereunder shall be a waiver of any preceding or subsequent breach or default. The section headings are for convenience only.

  You agree to indemnify, hold harmless, and release us, and each of our respective subsidiaries, affiliates, agents, licensees, employees, and third parties against any and all claims, damages, cost, and expenses (including attorney’s fees) arising from and related to your use of the site, and any content contained in the site and/or any transaction you enter into with a third party based on information or contacts obtained from the site.

  **No Agency Relationships**  
The franchisees of Which Wich Franchise, Inc. have no agency relationship with Which Wich, Inc. and/or Which Wich Franchise, Inc. Each entity acts independently of one another.
